Guide to the Lingnan Foundation Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Program Records, 1979-2010; Series IV
  - Zhongshan University (Sun Yat-sen University)
    - Library / DLIS
      - Library administrators' lecture tour of China, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Faculty/Staff Development
      - Emerging Disciplines Program, 1993-1994 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Emerging Disciplines Program, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - Emerging Disciplines Program, 1996-1999 (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Faculty Development Fund Program, 1996-1997 (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - Faculty Development Fund Program, 1998-1999 (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Faculty Development Fund Program, 2000-2003 (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - Faculty Development Fund Program, 2005-2009 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Staff Training Program, 1985-1989 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Staff Training Program, 1990-1991 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Staff Training Program, 1992-1994 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Staff Training Program, 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Staff Training Program, 2004-2007 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Schools and Departments
      - Anthropology Department, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Anthropology / Lingnan Regional Ethnicity Project, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - Anthropology / Lingnan Regional Ethnicity Project, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Anthropology / Lingnan Regional Ethnicity Project, 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - Anthropology / Lingnan Regional Ethnicity Project, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - Anthropology / Lingnan Regional Ethnicity Project, Centre for Historical Anthropology, 1998-2000, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 12)
      - Foreign Languages and Literature, School of, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Foreign Languages and Literature, 1993-1994 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Foreign Languages and Literature, 1995-1996 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - Foreign Languages and Literature, 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - Foreign Languages and Literature, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Foreign Languages and Literature, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Foreign Languages and Literature, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Foreign Languages and Literature, 2002-2004 (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - Management, School of, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - Management, 1986-1987 (Box 20, Folder 10)
      - Management, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 11)
      - Management, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 12)
      - Management, 1990-1992 (Box 20, Folder 13)
      - Medical College, 1979-1998 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Network Education, School of, 2001-2004 (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - Social Work Department, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - Sociology Department, 1992-1993 (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - Sociology, 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - Sociology, 1996-1998 (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - Sociology, 2001-2003 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Building renovations
      - Information re. historic Lingnan campus, Coles Lodge, 1994-1996, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - Grant Hall - includes photographs, blueprints, 1997-2002, no date (Box 21, Folder 8)
      - Martin Hall, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous initiatives, projects
      - Environment, 1988-1994 (Box 21, Folder 10)
      - Equipment purchases, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 11)
      - Interdisciplinary Teaching, 2004-2005 (Box 21, Folder 12)
      - Liberal Learning - Harmonized Coexistence, 2004-2006 (Box 21, Folder 13)
      - Liberal Learning- Mathematics Modeling, 2004-2006 (Box 21, Folder 14)
      - Liberal Learning - Theater Troupe, 2004-2008 (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Liberal Learning - Three Gorges Dam Field Investigation, 2004-2006 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Liberal Learning - miscellaneous proposals, 2007-2008 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Network / E-mail, 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Network / E-mail, 1996-1999 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Network - Wiring Student Dorms, Faculty Residences, 2000-2001 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - New Initiatives Fund projects, 2003-2004 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - President's Discretionary Fund, 1990-1994 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Red Buildings on Honglok Campus book, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - Remote Learning project, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - Social Change Basic Survey / Guangdong Development Institute, 1999-2004 (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - Report on various programs, 2006 (Box 29, Folder 2a)
  - Chinese University of Hong Kong
    - Chronological files, 1982-1983 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Chronological files, 1984-1985 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Chronological files, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Chronological files, 1988-1989 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Chronological files, 1990-1991 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Chronological files, 1992-1993 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Chronological files, 1994-2000 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Academic exchanges, 1991-1998 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Academic Visitors (Management Teachers) Programme, 1984-1991 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - C.K. Yang Research and Training Fund, 2000-2006 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Comparative Literature and Language Exchange Program, 1982-1985 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Comparative Literature and Language Exchange Program, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Comparative Literature and Language Exchange Program, 1988-1989 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Comparative Literature and Language Exchange Program, 1990-1991 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Comparative Literature and Language Exchange Program, 1992-1993 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Comparative Literature and Language Exchange Program, 1994-1996 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Comparative Literature and Language Exchange Program - publications, 1985, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Doctoral Business Administration Fellowship Program, 1977-1989 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Graduate Business Program, 1982-1997 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Lingnan Faculty Development Fellowship Program, 1980-1983 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - PRC Teachers Fellowship Award Program, 1980-1984 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Program on Sociology and the Study of Contemporary Chinese Society, 1981-1983 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Program on Sociology and the Study of Contemporary Chinese Society, 1984-1988 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Research Centre for Translation, 1985-1987 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Research Centre for Translation, 1988-1996 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Universities Service Centre, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous programs and projects
    - W. T. Chan Fellowships Program - U.C. Berkeley, 2003-2004 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - W. T. Chan Fellowships Program - Institute of International Education administration, 2006-2007 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Chen Su-Qing biography, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - China Bridges International / formerly China-Cornell Fellowship Program, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - China Bridges International / formerly China-Cornell Fellowship Program, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - China Bridges International / formerly China-Cornell Fellowship Program, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - China Bridges International / formerly China-Cornell Fellowship Program, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - China Bridges International, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - China Bridges International, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - China Bridges International, 2000-2003 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Committee on Scholarly Communication with China, 1984-1996 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Elisabeth Luce Moore Leadership Program - Institute of International Education administration, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Hong Kong-America Center, 1992-1994 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Hong Kong-America Center, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Hong Kong-America Center, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Hong Kong-America Center, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Hong Kong-America Center, 1998-2002 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Hong Kong-America Center, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Hong Kong Summer Service Program, 2004-2006 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Lingnan Alumni Association of Guangzhou, 1981-1985 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Lingnan Alumni Association of Guangzhou, 1986-1988 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Lingnan Alumni Association of Guangzhou, 1989-1990 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Lingnan Alumni Association of Guangzhou, 1991-1995 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Lingnan Education Organization Limited, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Lingnan Luncheon Club, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Lingnan Luncheon Club, 1988-1991 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Lingnan Luncheon Club, 1992-1993 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Lingnan Luncheon Club, 1994-1995 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - National Committee on United States-China Relations, 2000-2001 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Teachers College Seminar on Chinese Education, 2000-2003 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - University of Hong Kong - Programme in American Studies, 1998-1999 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - University of Hong Kong - Programme in American Studies, 2000-2003 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - University of Hong Kong - Interdisciplinary Teaching program, 2004 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - University of Pittsburgh - Sociology Department, 1982-1984 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - University of Pittsburgh - Sociology Department, 1994-1999 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - University of Pittsburgh - Sociology Department, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Vermont Law School / Sun Yat-sen University Partnership for Environmental Law in China, 2004-2006 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Vermont Law School / Sun Yat-sen University Partnership for Environmental Law in China, 2007 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Volunteers in Asia - Guangzhou English Training Centre for the Disabled, 1999-2001 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Williams College - Williams-in-Asia, 1978-1984 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Williams College - Center for Development Economics, 1984-1985 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Yale-China Association - Blatchford/Lanzhou project, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Yale-China Association - Blatchford/Lanzhou project, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Yale-China Association - Blatchford/Lanzhou project, 1981-1982 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Yale-China Association - miscellaneous, 1981-1982 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Yale-China Association - miscellaneous, 1983-1984 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Yale-China Association - miscellaneous, 1985-1991 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Yale-China Association - miscellaneous, 1997-2000 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Yale-China Association - miscellaneous, 2001-2003 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Yale-China Association - miscellaneous, 2004-2010 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Financial Records, 1974-2006; Series V
  - Financial statements, 1974-1979 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Financial statements, 1980-1985 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Financial statements, 1986-1991 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Financial statements, 1992-1996 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Financial statements, 1997-2000 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Financial statements, 2001-2006 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Internal Revenue Service, 1964-1974 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Internal Revenue Service, 1975-1979 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Internal Revenue Service, 1980-1982 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Internal Revenue Service, 1983-1986 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Internal Revenue Service, 1987-1989 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Internal Revenue Service, 1990-1991 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Internal Revenue Service, 1992-1994 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Investment management proposal, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 8)